Surya Narayanan

Product UI/UX Designer

Summary

I am a seasoned professional over 5+ Year with extensive experience in crafting exceptional visual experience and UX interfaces for digital products solution. My expertise lies in understanding and designing graphic solution based on clients requirement, and translating insights work consistently and accurately. Gathering user requirements, designing graphic elements and building navigation components.

Contact me

Address

Bangalore, KA, India

Work Type

Onsite, Hybrid and Remote

Mobile

+916369724601

Date of Birth

07.18.1998

Website

https://survadsign.github.io

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ surya-narayanan-609339156/

Email

suryandesigner@gmail.com

Skille

SKIIIS	
Figma	
User Research	
Advanced Prototyping	
Interaction Design	
Contextual Inquiry	
Cognitive Walkthrough	
Design Sprints	
Interaction Flow Journey	
Heuristic Evaluation	
Accessibility	

Work History

2021-05 -Present

Product Designer

eMudhra Technology Limited, Bengaluru, India

- Experience in conducting user research and extracting valuable insights to inform product localisation decisions
- Design and deliver high quality user interactions, experiences, by mapping experiences and journeys, create concepts, Process flows and prototype. Create wireframes on time and to expected level of quality
- Undergone process in ideation / design sprints in diverse, multidisciplinary cross functional teams.
- Expanding the team in crafting and developing our new ventures and products funnel.
- Communicating effectively and collaborate with team members to put ideas (from problems) into action and iterate on them.
- Taking ownership of products and Ability to lead the team, Assign task and Manage the workload.
- Proven experience using tools like Figma, Miro, Adobe XD, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator etc
- Validating the redesigned application as prototypedriven / from a user perspective
- Strong Collaboration and Communication Skill with Client/Stakeholders and team mates discussing rough drafts and samples to initiate conversation effectively.
- Creative and professional way projecting graphic designs for the requirements (Images, Sketches, GIf, Logo etc.

Wireframes	
User Centred Design	
Website Analytics	
Interface Design	
Design System	
Visual Design	
Usability Design	
Affinity Mapping	
Agile Development	
Graphic Designs	
Vector Illustrations	
Mood Board	
Logo	
Brochure/ Banners	
Video Editing	

Tools

Figma	
Adobe XD	
Sketch	
Adobe Photoshop	
Adobe Illustrator	
FigJam	
Balsamiq	
Blender	
Affinity Designer	•
Adobe Effects	

Programming

HTML	
CSS	
Bootstrap	
Javascript	

2020-01 - 2021-04

UI/UX Designer

CIOC FMCG Private Ltd, Bengaluru, India

- Developing user friendly interfaces and interaction flows of 10+ applications for mobile and web applications.
- Demonstrated experience proving designs, hypotheses and recommendations through use of data or validated evidence, and providing commercial rationale for decisions
- Collaborating with team for consistency of the user experience while taking it step by step to the next level.
- Worked in SaaS platforms, B2B, B2C and/or enterprise products.
- Executed various visual design stages from concept to final hand-off development.

2019-01 - 2019-12

UX Designer

Haso Technology Ltd, Madurai, India

- · Practiced UX research under a senior UX Designer
- Get in touch with stake holders to understand what is the basic requirements and how to develop a product.
- Have strong understanding of User Experience Design and Design Thinking process

Education

2015/08 -2019/05

Bachelor's Degree

Electronics and Communication Engineer

K.L.N College of Engineering, Madurai, India